ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
(遠藤達哉原創作品 連載於集英社《SHONEN JUMP PLUS》)
Vincent,
威森特
I love you.
我愛你
This isn't right, Sonia.
不可以這樣,索妮雅小姐
I have a fiancée I left behind in the West.
我在西國已經有未婚妻了
But that's just an arranged marriage!
但那只是父母安排的婚姻吧!
I'll help you forget about her!
我會讓你忘記她的!
MISSION:36 PART A: BERLINT IN LOVE
劇名:任務:36 A Part:伯林特戀曲
No, we mustn't Sonia! I can't breathe...
不行,索妮雅小姐! 我要喘不過氣了...
Anya!
安妮亞!
I'm out shopping near your house right now,
我剛好到妳家附近逛街買東西
but can I stop by your place?
現在可以順路去妳家坐坐嗎?
I can? Great, thank you! I'll be there!
妳說可以?太好了,我馬上過去!
Good day, Anya!
妳好啊,安妮亞!
Please tell me you're not home alone!
妳一個人嗎?應該不是一個人吧!
Becky, are you the teleporting Shashasha-man?
貝琪,妳是瞬間移動的蝦蝦蝦曼?
I will definitely meet Mr. Loid today
今天一定要見到洛伊德先生
and ask him to go out with me.
然後我要跟他提出交往!
Miss, you must not have an affair.
不可以搞不倫戀喔,大小姐
Father, Becky is here.
父親,貝琪來了
Hey, welcome.
嗨,歡迎妳來
It's Mr. Loid in the flesh!
是活生生的洛伊德先生!
Miss, you mustn't forget your greetings.
大小姐,您也要打招呼喔
Um... um...
那個...
Hello. Thank you for having me...
您...您好,打擾了
Sorry for visiting unannounced, Mr. Forger.
冒昧來訪真是不好意思,佛傑先生
No problem at all.
不會,哪裡的話
My daughter's happy to have her friend stop by for a visit.
我女兒也很開心朋友來家裡找她玩
Hello, Miss Becky.
妳好啊,貝琪小姐
Miss Becky...
貝琪小姐...
- Miss Becky... - Lo...
- 貝琪小姐... - 洛...
Thanks for always being so good to my daughter.
謝謝妳一直以來都跟我女兒這麼好
A star, hashtag, triangle, ampersand, smiley face, hot spring, heart...
星號、井字號、三角形 AND符號、笑臉、溫泉、愛心...
Is this a code?
是暗號嗎?
Miss, please get up.
大小姐,快起來
It's bad manners to lie down on the ground in someone else's house.
隨便躺在別人家的地板上很失禮
I love you.
戀愛了
I remember seeing someone like this before.
安妮亞記得之前也見過一樣的人
LOVE
(喜歡)
Please behave well, Miss.
那麼,大小姐接下來也要注意禮節喔
I'll be back to pick you up.
我會再回來接您
Okay.
好
Thank you for looking after her.
我們家大小姐就麻煩您照顧了
Sure.
好的
The way she carries herself tells me
那位管家的儀態舉止透露出
that she's a former experienced soldier.
她原本應該是經驗老道的軍人
It's the Blackbell family after all.
真不愧是布萊克貝爾家族
Do you want to explore Anya's house?
妳要在安妮亞家裡探險嗎?
Come to think of it, it's my first time inside.
說起來,我還是第一次踏進妳家呢
This is the living room.
這裡是客廳
What? I thought this was the storage area by the entrance!
什麼?我以為是玄關旁的收納區呢!
This is Anya's room!
這裡是安妮亞的房間!
Oh my, it's much smaller than my Wiesel's doghouse.
天啊,這比我家 維瑟爾的狗屋要小很多耶
Isn't it suffocating?
不會覺得住得很窒息嗎?
Let's quit exploring.
還是不要探險了吧
If you want.
這樣嗎?
By the way, where's Mrs. Forger?
話說回來,夫人在哪裡?
Mother took Bond on a walk.
母親帶彭德去散步了
This is my chance!
我的機會來了!
Mr. Loid!
洛伊德先生!
This isn't right, Miss Becky. I have a wife.
這樣不行,貝琪小姐 我已經有家室了
It was an arranged marriage, right?
那是父母安排的婚姻吧?
UNFOUNDED
(無憑無據)
But...
可是...
I'll use my charms to help you forget about her!
我會用我的魅力讓你忘了她!
Miss Becky!
貝琪小姐!
Becky as my mom?!
貝琪當安妮亞的母親?
I'm sure it will make Anya happy if I become her mother.
如果我變成安妮亞的母親 她一定也會很高興
Let's live in this spacious house.
新家就住這棟寬敞的房子吧
It's a castle!
是城堡耶!
Come Anya, let's go to school together in my helicopter.
走吧,安妮亞,一起搭直升機去上學
Mother!
母親!
A first-rate chef will prepare our meals every day.
每天都會有一流的主廚料理三餐
- Delicious! - Yummy!
- 真好吃! - 好吃!
The servants will take care of all the tiresome chores.
累人的家事就交給僕人去做吧
Let's go out and play.
我們出去玩吧
Yay!
好耶!
It's not bad!
其實也不錯耶!
Sorry, Mother.
母親,對不起
I'm leaning more towards Becky because of the first-rate chef.
為了一流的主廚 我要稍微幫一下貝琪的忙
Father! Come play with us.
父親,來跟我們玩嘛
Nice assist, Anya!
助攻真是到位,安妮亞!
Play with you guys?
跟妳們玩?
We can just talk if you'd like.
只...只是聊聊天的話也可以的
Oh... um... ah... I'm Becky Blackbell.
那...那個...我是貝琪布萊克貝爾
Yes, I'm aware of that.
嗯,我知道喔
First-rate chef! First-rate chef!
一流的主廚!
The Blackbell family is very famous.
布萊克貝爾家族非常有名
I already knew about you before you became Anya's classmate.
在妳跟安妮亞當同學之前 我就知道妳了
As an important source of intel.
妳可是重要的情報管道
He knew about me from long ago?
很久以前就知道我了?
I've already secured a few outlets to gain intel from Blackbell,
雖然已經掌握了 幾個蒐集布萊克貝爾的情報管道
but I might be able to get something out of the daughter.
不過從他們女兒身上 也許能得到什麼情報
It's worth trying.
值得一試
Father is always thinking about work.
父親總是在想工作的事
How is your father doing?
妳父親還好嗎?
I hear he's been busy restructuring his business.
聽說因為產業重組 他好像很忙的樣子
Ah...
那個...
Yes, but Papa is really nice,
是啊,不過爸爸對我很好
so he plays with me on his days off.
休假的時候一定會陪我玩
We went to the movies the other day.
上次還去看了電影
Next time, I want to go with you.
下次我想跟你一起去
I see. What did you watch?
這樣啊,你們看了什麼電影?
Was it that movie theater along the river?
難道是在河邊那家電影院看的?
There are lots of great restaurants around there.
那一帶有很多很好吃的餐廳
Her father's time off.
她父親的休假時間
Area of activity, habits, and food preferences.
活動範圍、嗜好跟喜歡的食物
There's countless useful information.
有用的情報多得很
The movie was a love story...
那個...我們看了愛情片
Is he trying to gauge my preferences?
他...他想了解我的喜好嗎?
Even the restaurants?
所以才提到餐廳嗎?
Wait, is he asking me out to eat? Is he?
等等,難道 他想約我去吃飯?是這樣嗎?
You must be close with your father.
妳跟妳父親感情一定很好
Do you go out with your family often?
你們常常全家一起出門嗎?
Do you play together at home too?
在家裡也會一起玩遊戲嗎?
Currently,
目前
nothing suggests that Blackbell Industries is taking part in planning a war.
布萊克貝爾重工業並沒有參戰的跡象
But it won't hurt to gather intel while taking future possibilities into account.
不過考慮到未來的可能性 先蒐集情報也無妨
Pa... Papa likes chess.
爸...爸爸喜歡下西洋棋
I have no idea how to play it, but I always have to play against him.
我其實不會玩,但他總是找我陪他玩
Oh... and...
還有...還有就是...
I didn't think he'd express such interest in my family!
沒想到他對我的家庭這麼有興趣!
Mr. Loid, are you...
洛伊德先生,難道你...
thinking of me as someone to share your future with?
把我看成了共度未來的對象嗎?
He looks somewhat serious!
不知為何他看起來好認真!
This is fun.
真有趣
We're back.
我們回來了
Oh? Welcome, Becky!
咦?歡迎妳來,貝琪小姐!
She's here! The last boss!
來了,最終BOSS!
- Right when Mr. Loid started - First-rate chef!
- 偏偏在洛伊德先生開始 - 一流的主廚...
- expressing interest in me!
- 對我展現出興趣的時候!
Hello, Mrs. Forger.
夫...夫人好
Oh my, how cute.
哎呀,真可愛
Look Becky, this is Bond!
貝琪妳看,這就是我們家的彭德!
Mr. Loid's heart is leaning towards me right now!
洛伊德先生的心已經倒向我這邊了!
- Look Becky! - You're so close, Becky!
- 快看啊,貝琪! - 就快成功了,貝琪!
You have to give it your all right now!
現在必須使出渾身解數才行!
I'll use everything I learned from the drama!
把從連續劇學到的都用上!
Loid,
洛伊德先生
I bought the ingredients for dinner.
我買好了晚餐要用的食材
Thanks, Yor.
謝謝妳,約兒
Is she trying to show off her competence as a wife?
她是想展現自己是多賢慧的妻子嗎?
How naive.
太天真了
You can't move Mr. Loid's heart with something trivial like that.
洛伊德先生的心 才不會因為這種小把戲而動搖
Father and Mother are already married.
父親跟母親已經結婚了
Jonathan in Berlint in Love said
《伯林特戀曲》的強納森說過
that even after marriage, a man wants his mate to maintain her womanly appeal.
婚後的男人 依舊會希望伴侶維持女性的魅力
Hm?
怎麼?
What? His reaction is a bit dull.
奇怪?他的反應有點平淡耶
Maybe I needed to glance upwards a bit more.
也許是剛剛拋媚眼拋得不夠嗎?
Tommy said that it's sexy whenever girls tie
湯米也說過女生綁髮跟鬆髮時
and untie their hair.
是很性感的啊
Becky must be really happy because she's been wanting
貝琪小姐一定很開心,畢竟她之前
to see you for a very long time, Loid. Is she expressing her happiness?
就一直很想要見你,洛伊德先生 她是在表現她有多開心嗎?
Oh... hm.
哦...應該吧
I brought some tea.
茶準備好囉
Loid, why don't you sit over there on the couch?
洛伊德先生 你怎麼不坐沙發那邊呢?
Mr. Loid is sitting next to me! He's next to me!
洛伊德先生坐在我旁邊! 他就在我旁邊!
Mrs. Forger must be crazy. Why is she aiding her enemy?
夫人一定是瘋了 怎麼會出手幫助敵人?
She must have accepted her defeat after seeing me flip my hair.
一定是在看完我的撥髮魅力後 自嘆不如吧
This is your chance, Becky! Go in for the kill!
這是機會啊,貝琪 要一鼓作氣打敗她啊!
It seems like she's ill...
她看起來好像身體不太舒服...
Um... Mr. Loid, let's continue with our discussion from earlier...
那個...洛伊德先生,剛才的話題...
You were showing interest in my family.
您對人家的家庭有興趣嗎?
How formal.
“先生”?
Oh sorry, I didn't mean to pry. I was just curious since your family is so famous.
抱歉,我無意刺探隱私 只是出於追星心態才問的
Oh crap. Maybe I went too far, thinking that she's just a child.
糟糕了,把對方看成小孩 不小心問過頭了嗎?
What? You were just playing with me?
什麼?您只是在玩弄我嗎?
What are you saying?
妳在說什麼呢?
Yor will get the wrong idea.
約兒小姐會誤會的
Oh, Loid is so impressive.
洛伊德先生真厲害
He was playing with Becky while I was away?
所以我還沒回來之前 他一直在陪貝琪玩嗎?
He's so nice!
真是溫柔呢!
Look at Mrs. Forger's smile! She must be confident she beat me!
夫人那個悠哉的笑容! 她一定是很有信心能贏過我!
You really think I don't have a chance with Mr. Loid?
果然我跟洛伊德先生是沒戲唱了嗎?
I'm going to lose the first-rate chef.
一流的主廚要沒了
It's time to go for broke!
這樣的話就乾脆豁出去了!
It's the tactic Penelope used on Tommy!
這是潘妮洛普對湯米用的最終奧義!
I think I'm a little drunk.
人家好像有點喝醉了
It's just tea.
不是吧,妳喝的是紅茶
According to Berlint in Love,
根據《伯林特戀曲》
this is the prohibited technique to make any man fall for you!
這招百分百可以讓任何男人墜入情網
There's no turning back now! The fight is on, Mrs. Forger!
這下不能回頭了! 一決勝負吧,夫人!
Yor, don't misunderstand...
約兒,別誤會...
Oh no!
不好了!
Did I serve alcohol to a child?
難道我給小孩子倒酒了嗎?
What should I do?
怎麼辦才好啊?
No, this is just tea.
不是的,這只是紅茶
Perhaps the tea leaves were fermented too long...
也許茶葉發酵太久了...
What?
幹嘛?
Let's go to the hospital!
立刻去醫院吧!
Wait!
等...等一下啊...
Yor!
約兒小姐!
Are you okay, Becky?
沒事吧,貝琪小姐?
Do you feel nauseous?
會覺得想吐嗎?
I'm okay! So put me down!
我沒事,所以快放我下來!
Acute alcohol poisoning shouldn't be underestimated!
不可以小看酒精急性中毒!
It's not about that!
不是啊,不是那樣的!
Which doctor should I take her to?
不過應該要看哪一科才對?
Let's go to the emergency room!
總之先去急診室好了!
We'll be there soon! Stay awake!
我們馬上就到!保持清醒!
Don't fall asleep! You'll die!
不要睡著了,會死掉的!
You're thinking of something else.
妳完全誤會了啦
Don't forget to breathe!
別忘了要呼吸!
That's something else too.
也不是那樣啦
Wait, Mrs. Forger. You've got it all wrong.
等等,夫人完全誤會我了,其實我...
I lied because I wanted to go out with Mr. Loid.
我說謊了 因為我想跟洛伊德先生在一起
I'm not drunk!
我沒喝醉!
What?
什麼?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry!
對不起,真的對不起!
I'm so glad you're okay.
妳沒事真是太好了
What?
什麼?
Can you stand?
站得起來嗎?
You're not going to get mad at me?
妳...妳不對我發火嗎?
Why would I? You're safe and well.
怎麼會呢?妳平安無事啊
Oh well, there's the thing with Mr. Loid too...
不是,關於洛伊德先生的事也是...
It makes me happy to know that Loid is loved.
知道洛伊德先生有人喜歡 我覺得很高興呢
He is a lovely person after all.
畢竟他確實是很討人喜歡啊
Oh my!
什麼!
She's so broad-minded!
人家心胸多寬大啊!
She's okay with affairs?
她可以接受不倫戀嗎?
I should be the one to apologize.
該道歉的人是我
I misunderstood and dragged you out here.
我誤會了妳,還把妳拖來這裡
No, it's my fault.
不,這都是我的錯
Compared to Loid, I'm so useless.
跟洛伊德先生相比,我真的很沒用
But Mr. Loid chose you!
但...但是洛伊德先生選擇了妳啊!
How did you shoot and capture Mr. Loid's heart? I'm so curious!
妳是怎麼射中 洛伊德先生的心房的?好好奇喔!
Shoot and capture...
射中...
No, I didn't shoot Loid at all!
我沒射洛伊德先生東西啊!
I don't use bows and arrows to begin with!
而且我根本不用弓箭...
Loid chose me because...
洛伊德先生會選我是因為...
I can't say that it was because we matched each other's requirements.
總不能說是因為符合彼此的要求吧
I only remember vaguely, but one time he told me,
我只是大概記得,有一回他說了
"Because you're strong."
“因為妳很強大”
Because you're strong?
“因為妳很強大”?
Mr. Loid likes strong women?
洛伊德先生喜歡強大的女性?
Come to think of it, Mrs. Forger is very strong! And tough!
說起來這位夫人 確實很強,而且還很壯!
Hey!
喂!
There they are!
找到他們了
Becky!
貝琪!
Becky, you forgot your bag.
貝琪,妳忘了妳的包包
Mr. Loid, did you come running after me because you were worried?
洛伊德先生是因為擔心我 所以才追過來的嗎?
Your bag.
包包
I'm strong.
強大...
I have to show him how strong I am!
我得向他展現出我有多強大!
How can I do that?
該怎麼做呢?
That's it!
有了!
Oh, I have the sudden urge to hit something with a hammer.
人家突然很想用槌子打什麼東西
What kind of urge is that? I don't understand rich kids at all.
突然很想?真搞不懂有錢人家的小孩
Sir, can I try this?
大叔,我可以玩這個嗎?
What? You have any money, Missy?
什麼?小姐,妳身上有錢嗎?
Chef!
主廚...
- Let's do this! - Chef!
- 要上了喔! - 主廚...
Chef!
主廚...
You give up?
妳要放棄嗎?
I'm a weak woman.
我是個脆弱的女人
I'm a weak, worthless woman.
脆弱又沒用的女人
Are you all right?
妳...妳沒事吧?
At this rate, I will never catch Mr. Loid's attention.
再這樣下去的話 洛伊德先生永遠不會注意到我
Oh, I see.
原來啊
Becky probably wanted to give the grand prize to Loid as a gift.
貝琪應該是想贏得頭獎 送給洛伊德先生當禮物
Let me try it one time.
換我試試看
All right.
好
Grand prize!
頭獎!
- Oh... yay... - Grand prize!
- 成...成功了... - 頭獎!
I should've held back a little more.
不小心用了太多力氣了
This is the meaning of strength.
這就是強大的真諦
Mr. Loid is staring at his wife!
洛伊德先生目不轉睛地看著他夫人!
So it's true that you like strong women, huh?
果然是這樣嗎? 他喜歡強大的女性嗎?
Yor...
約兒小姐...
It's not what you think, Loid!
不是你想的那樣,洛伊德先生!
I once trained under a professional hammer wielder!
以前我曾經受過 專業揮槌大師的訓練!
Those rounded eyes!
那雙園滾滾的眼睛!
That's definitely the look of love!
分明就是墜入愛河的眼神!
I'm no match for you, Mrs. Forger.
我果然還是敵不過夫人啊
What?
什麼?
You have the mind and heart as broad as the sky, and the strength of the earth!
妳的心胸有如天空般寬廣 力氣又有如大地般強悍!
You're the perfect lady.
根本是無懈可擊的淑女
Please be my master and teach me the way!
我想拜妳為師,教教我吧!
I want to become strong like you!
我想變得跟妳一樣強悍!
L... like me?
跟...我一樣?
Okay! Let's train together!
我明白了,那就一起特訓吧!
Okay, Mrs. Forger!
好的,夫人!
And someday I will win over Mr. Loid...
總有一天我會把洛伊德先生搶過來...
I'm here to pick up Miss Becky.
我來接您了,大小姐
Ya!
嘿咻!
That's not right, Becky.
不是那樣喔,貝琪小姐
You must twist your hips a little more. Like this!
腰部要再轉過去一點,就像這樣!
Ya!
嘿咻!
- Ya!
- 嘿咻!
- Is this a déjà vu?
- 這場景似曾相識呢
- My mother is more fun after all. - Ya!
- 果然還是母親比較好玩 - 嘿咻!
BERLINT GENERAL HOSPITAL THURSDAY
(伯林特綜合醫院,星期四)
Doctor Forger, you'll be on vacation starting tomorrow, right?
佛傑醫生明天要去休假了,對吧?
Sorry for the inconvenience.
是的,抱歉
No, you're a workaholic, so you need this vacation.
哪裡,你一直在工作 確實需要好好放個假
Relax and have fun.
務必要好好玩喔
I'm so envious. Please tell us all about your trip when you return!
好羨慕喔,醫生 回來後記得分享旅途中的趣事喔!
Will do. Thank you.
當然好,謝謝你們
Thank you for dealing with any inconveniences while I'm gone.
我不在的時候,就拜託各位多幫忙了
WISE SAFEHOUSE G
(WISE藏身處G)
That's the summary of the mission this time.
這是這次任務的總結
Any questions?
有什麼問題嗎?
No.
沒有,沒問題
I'm counting on you, Nightfall.
那就有勞妳了,夜帷
Oh, and one more thing.
對了,還有一件事
Look through this.
這個妳也看看吧
I was planning on giving these missions to Twilight after his vacation.
黃昏休假回來後 我打算把這些任務交給他
But plans have changed.
但計畫有變
Sorry, but this is urgent. Can you take on a few of them?
雖然抱歉,但這是急件 妳能接下其中幾項任務嗎?
Of course I'll assign some to the other agents too.
當然我會把其中幾項派給其他特務
No, I can do it all on my own.
不用了,這些我自己可以全部解決
I'm glad you're willing, but you have your own current mission as well.
妳有這份心實在太好了 不過妳自己也有任務在身
I don't want my agents to get exhausted by overworking themselves.
我並不希望我底下的特務 因為埋首工作而過度勞累
But I highly doubt there is anyone else besides me who can complete these tasks.
不過,我非常懷疑除我之外 還有誰能完成這些任務
Fine. But don't push yourself too hard.
好吧,不過妳別太勉強自己了
Agent Twilight, WISE's most skilled spy.
WISE最頂尖的間諜,特務黃昏
Missions assigned to a skilled spy such as him,
這樣出類拔萃的間諜,交給他的任務
are anything but easy to accomplish.
必定都能輕鬆完成
But this will be a big opportunity for me.
不過 這對我來說,就是個大好機會
Twilight taught me many valuable things.
黃昏前輩教給我很多重要的事情
Like the skills necessary to be a spy, and fighting techniques.
像是作為間諜的基本功以及戰鬥技巧
I will make full use of all that I was taught and complete this mission.
我會將學到的知識 在這次的任務上發揮得淋漓盡致
And...
然後...
after I perfectly complete my mission...
在我完滿達成任務之際...
I will take the place as his wife...
我就要佔據前輩妻子的位置
All right. I'm sure this will make him realize
好,我確信這個會讓前輩明白
that I'm most suited to be his partner.
我才是最適合他的伴侶
But...
可是...
this is not enough.
這樣還不夠
It's not enough for me to be certain of my victory
這樣還不足以擔保我一定會
against Yor Briar.
贏過約兒布萊爾
I need to do more in order to become Mrs. Forger.
必須再多加把勁才能當上佛傑夫人
More...
再加把勁...
MONDAY MORNING
(星期一早上)
Those are the files I put together of your patients while you were away.
這裡是前輩不在的時候 我所整理的病人檔案
This is helpful.
真是幫了大忙了
I missed seeing him the last three days. Love you.
這三天來我都好想見到前輩,超愛你
- How was your vacation? - Did you find any major faults?
- 你假期過得如何呢? - 作為行動代號“梟”的妻子
- Anything out of the ordinary? - Concerning your wife for Operation Strix?
- 有不尋常的地方嗎? - 有什麼重大失誤嗎?
There was back-breaking work to deal with
安妮亞的脾氣跟潛在的炸彈危機
like Anya's tantrums and a potential bombing.
真的是非常勞心勞力的工作
No, nothing in particular.
沒有,沒什麼特別的
I see.
這樣啊
Dammit.
可惡
How about you?
那妳那邊怎麼樣?
Anything out of the ordinary while I was away?
我不在的時候 有什麼不尋常的事嗎?
I worked hard on missions because I wanted to be useful to you.
為了成為前輩得力的夥伴 我很努力地執行任務
Next time, I will make sure to win against that woman.
下次我一定會贏過那個女人
So please choose me for the role of your wife.
拜託選我扮演你的妻子吧
No, nothing in particular.
沒有,沒什麼特別的
I see.
這樣啊
Nightfall said that?
夜帷說的?
Yeah.
對
She was fired up and told me to leave it all up to her.
她鬥志滿滿地告訴我 把所有任務都交給她
She impressively completed the work.
而且漂亮地把工作完成了呢
I can't believe Nightfall covered my work.
夜帷竟然接下我所有的工作
Even when she had her own mission to complete.
明明她自己也有任務在身
SOUVENIRS
(伴手禮)
By the way, I passed out souvenirs to everyone, and there's one left.
說起來,我給每個人都送了伴手禮 不過還剩一份
Would you like it?
妳要嗎?
She's glaring at me!
她在瞪我!
What? What does this mean?
怎麼了?這是什麼意思?
Thank you.
謝謝你
Excuse me.
告辭了
Oh...
咦...
I love you. I love you.
喜歡...
- I love you. - I thought it was now or never.
- 喜歡... - 我心想再不說就沒機會了
So I said it.
所以我就說了
- I see. - Oh, Ms. Fiona!
- 原來如此 - 費歐娜小姐!
- Good morning.
- 早安
LOVE
(喜歡)
MISSION:37 PART OF THE FAMILY
(任務:37 家族的一員)
Subtitle translation by: Lili Morita
字幕翻譯:洪貞韻